looks-awesome.com 2015-12-31

# Privacy Policy — Looks Awesome — Themes & Plugins

Your privacy is very important to us. Looks-Awesome.com doesn’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights. Looks-Awesome.com doesn’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our site.

This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Looks-Awesome.com and how it is used.

### Visitors

Like most website operators, Looks-Awesome.com collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Looks-Awesome.com’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how visitors use the website.

### Cookies

Looks-Awesome.com uses cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. Visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the Looks-Awesome.com website.

### Policy Acceptance

By using this website, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. Although most changes are likely to be minor, Looks-Awesome.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Looks-Awesome.com’s sole discretion.

### Contact Us

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at hello[at]looks-awesome[dot]com.
